Guide to the Mildred Warner papers, 1997-2006
Warner, Mildred papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Mildred Warner papers, 1997-2006
15-2-3719
Warner, Mildred.
1 cubic foot.
Correspondence, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, proposals, memoranda, conference material concerning the Child Care and Economic Development project.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Professor in the Dept. of City and Regional Planning, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, proposals, memoranda, conference material concerning the Child Care and Economic Development project.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Warner, Mildred; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University.Dept. of City and Regional Planning.; Cornell University.Child Care and Economic Development Project.
Subjects:
Day care centers--New York (State)--Tompkins County.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Pre 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Child Care Data for Tompkins County, May 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Case Study Bright Horizons by Kim Lazris, March 24, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Child Care Tax Credit Compared to Dependent Care Reimbursement Account, November 10, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cornell University Childcare Initiative, December 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Child Care Data for Tompkins County, December 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Grant application Child Care Quality and Consumer Education (Federal Research Funds), January 18, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meeting notes Sue Dale-Hall Jun 3, June 3, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meeting agenda and notes CCE Day Care Work Group Jun 16, June 16, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Grant application: Addressing the Challenges of Welfare Reform: Ensuring the Availability of Quality Day Care for all Families, June 30, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Memo HIPPY program, October 18, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meeting notes Child Care Trends and Emerging State Models, November 5, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Marin County Summary, November 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina Summary, November 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Email Martha Armstrong case studies, November 17, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meeting notes Sue Dale-Hall and Rory Thorpe Nov 22, November 22, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Email and notes Sara Michaelckuck day care project discussion, November 22, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- CRP 418/618-ARME 634 Spring, 2000 and Related Child Care Work (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Course announcement and syllabus, January 28, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class notes Jan 28, January 28, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notes from Louise Stoney presentation, January 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Model for determining individual family shortfall by income, January 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Tompkins County demographic data, January 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Tompkins County standards for determining legibility for services, January 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Email Sue Day Hall Community Fund Proposal, February 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting notes Feb 4, February 4, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class notes Feb 11, February 11, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting notes Feb 11, February 11, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Project components and timelines, February 11, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Porus Oldapadwala presentation, February 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bill Meyers presentation, February 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Proposal Community Foundation, February 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agenda Day Care Council Board of Directors, February 24, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Day Care Costs to Take a Bounce, February 29, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting agenda and notes Mar 13, March 13, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting notes March 26, March 26, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Needs Assessment email and survey, March 30, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Email fund design, March 30, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Opperman meeting (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Survey of Child Care Needs, April 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting notes Day Care Providers April 11, April 11, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting notes April 14, April 14, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce meeting agenda, April 18, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Email Sue Day Hall, April 19, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting with Mary Opperman, April 20, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Draft memo: Community Meeting on Day Care Subsidy Fund (Final draft unavailable), April 20, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting notes Apr 21, April 21, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting notes Cornell April 28, April 28, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting agenda Early Education Partnership April 28, April 28, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Robert Smith Award information, April 28, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cost/demand projection, May 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Article Ithaca Journal: Leaders Examine Vouchers, May 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Article Ithaca Times "Helping Hands: Student Study Finds Funding for Day Care Initiative", September 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - APA award application (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Misc Notes (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Fall, 2000 Child Care Work and Cornell Child Care Fund (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting notes and program Day Care and Child Development Council of Tompkins County Jun 15, June 15, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting notes Work Force Advisory Committee, June 19, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Community Partnership Committee agenda and notes, June 27, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Description Rochester Early Childhood Development Initiative (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Community Child Care Fund Objectives, Summer 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting notes Jul 31, July 31, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting notes Sep 27, September 27, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting notes ECE Investment Fund Model Oct 3, October 3, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Article summaries of Louise Stoney works in prep for presentation, October 15, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting notes Oct 16, October 16, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Louise Stoney presentation meeting(s) notes/announcement, October 20, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Early Education Partnership materials, October 21, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bill Meyers email securitization, October 25, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting notes Oct 25, October 25, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting notes Nov 7, November 7, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting notes Nov 20, November 20, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Child Care/Fund Work Spring, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Article Cornell Introduces New Child Care Grant in For Your Benefit, Spring 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Meeting notes Bonnie Cohen Mar 12, March 12, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Note Sue Dale-Hall on Community Fund (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Child Care Needs Assessment Tompkins County, May 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letter and materials Mildred Warner recommendation of Early Education Partnership to NCAA, May 30, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Grant application and guidelines The Early Education Partnership of Tompkins County (Faculty Fellows in Service), June 15, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Child Care/Fund Work Spring, 2001 Tompkins County (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Email to Marvin McKinney request Kellogg Foundation grant (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Grant RFP Dept HHS Child Care Policy Research Discretionary Grants, June 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Grant RFP Aspen Institute, July 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Ken Reardon and Steven Preston on Day Care Initiatives paper, July 23, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting notes Day Care Partnership Aug 27, August 27, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Email Marjorie Olds care for drug court participants, September 29, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting notes Oct 1, October 1, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting notes Nov 2, November 2, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting notes Louise Stoney Nov 2, November 2, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting notes Liz Peters (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting agenda and related materials Early Education Partnership, November 12, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Community Financing Project in Tompkins County: Subsidies Program Evaluation, December 1, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting notes Day Care Council Dec, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting notes job description discussion, December 3, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report Tompkins County Chamber of Commerce, Winter 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- CRP 618 and Other Child Care Work Spring, 2002 Tompkins County (Box 1, Folder 6-8)
  - Meeting notes and proposal April workshop (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proposed sub-project for Cornell students with background materials, January 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Government Policy Workshop: Goals, January 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - New Goals (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting notes and paper Elizabeth Peters, February 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Email Sue Dale-Hall student projects, February 1, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Email and concept paper Louise Stoney, February 7, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Summary of 2001-2002 Cornell Child Care Gent (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Group 1 work plan, February 9, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Group 3 work plan, February 9, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Summary Financing Child Care in the United States, February 9, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Early Ed Reports: Mapping the Future: Moving New York Closer to a Universal System of Child Care, February 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class notes Feb 15, February 15, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Exercise your right to affordable child care (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Group 1 revised work plan, February 20, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rose Ribeiro and Amy Erica Smith Workplan, February 20, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Group 3 revised workplan, February 20, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting notes and email summary Day Care Meeting Feb 21, February 21, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Email Mary Pat Dolan student meeting, February 22, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Discussions notes with Sue Dale-Hall student project (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting questions Feb 27, February 27, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting notes Mar 6, March 6, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Meeting notes Sue Dale-Hall Mar 7, March 7, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Meeting notes Chamber Mar 7, March 7, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Meeting notes Louise Stoney Mar 8, March 8, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Meeting notes Louise Stoney and Group 2, March 11, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chart 200% FPL 2002, March 12, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Work plan for Rose Ribero and Amy Erica Smith, March 15, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Class notes Mar 15, March 15, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Group 1 revised work plan, March 22, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rose Ribeiro and Amy Erica Smith Workplan, March 22, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Discussion of intersectoral relationships as measured by I/O models (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Email to class Mildred Warner, March 27, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Employer Focus Groups, March 27, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - List of deliverables, April 4, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Email Amy Erica transportation methodology, April 5, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rose Ribeiro and Amy Erica Smith workplan, April 5, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Email David Kay Implan, April 8, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Presentation Amy Erica Input-Output Analysis, May 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Presentation Rose Ribeiro Economic Impact of Child Care Subsidies, May 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General notes on methodology, May 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Economic Impact of Child Care Subsidies on Tompkins County (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Overview of available subsidies (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Worksheet to calculate supply and demand for care, May 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Input/Output Analysis promotional materials for Early Education Partnership, May 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Summary of child care subsidy criterion, May 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting agenda and materials for Early Education Partnership May 7, May 7, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting notes Chamber and DCC, May 16, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - List of reserve books used for class, May 21, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Day Care/ Child Care component of Tompkins County Consolidated Services Plan, May 30, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Misc Class Notes (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Child Care Work Fall, 2002 Tompkins Co (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meeting notes EEP Jun 7, June 7, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Tompkins County Child Care Investment Fund Report, July 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meeting notes EEP July, 2008, July 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meeting notes EEP Jul 8 and related materials, July 8, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Revision and Additions to Child Care Investment Fund, July 30, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Email Louise Stoney partnership with Abby Thorman, August 3, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Email Louise Stoney Child Care Investment Fund draft, August 4, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meeting agenda EEP, September 4, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lessons learned from interviews with child care partnerships in other cities/states, September 6, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Organizational charts for child care partnerships with other cities/states, September 6, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Spreadsheet summary of initiatives of child care partnerships, September 6, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Early Education Partnership Vision brochure, September 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Support questions and notes for Sue Zafonte Sennett NYS Dept of Early Childhood Services, September 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Organizational chart proposal for Tompkins County EEP child care financing model, September 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - EEP proposal to establish community-based scholarship program, September 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - EEP proposal to implement community-based scholarship fund, September 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meeting notes EEP Sep 16, September 16, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meeting notes EEP Oct 7, October 7, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Presentation Mildred Warner to Workforce Development Board, November 19, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Final Report Notebook and full set of materials, Spring 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Financing Child Care in Tompkins County Workshop - 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
- CRP 418/618-ARME 634 Spring, 2003 and Related Child Care Work-NYS (Box 1, Folder 12-14)
  - New York State's Competitiveness: A Scorecard of 12 States (Background), March 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - New York's Competitiveness: A Scorecard of 13 US Metropolitan Areas (Background), July 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Universal Preschool: Is it the Answer to Early Childhood Education (Background), November 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - US Census Bureau Report: Who's Minding the Kids (Background), July 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Diversifying and Rebuilding Local Economies (Background), August 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Child Care in New York State: A Patchwork of Polices (Background), November 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - New York City Budget Office: City Reliance on State and Federal Child Care Grows (Background), December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Syllabus CRP 418/618 Government Policy Workshop: Financing Child Care, January 22, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Class roster, January 22, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Goals for CRP workshop, January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Summary of methodologies for estimating the economic impact of child care, January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Promotional material child care fund, January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Child Care Development Fund Annual Aggregate Report Oct, 2001-Sep., 2002, January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Meeting notes survey, January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Workshop workplan Economic Impacts of Investment in Child Care, January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Summaries and notes Care and Equality, January 24, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Email Louise Stoney proposed class set up, January 28, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Class notes Jan 29, January 29, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Class notes Jan 31, January 31, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Memo to NYSCC Affiliates Executive Budget, January 31, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Email Louise Stoney Long Island Impact Study, February 3, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Balancing New York State's 2003-2004 Budget in an Economically Sensible Manner, February 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Meeting notes study set up Feb, 2003, February 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Class notes (handwritten and transcribed) Feb 7, February 7, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Meeting notes Community Partnership meeting Feb 7, February 7, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - List of NYS funded CCR&Rs Apr, 2000-Mar, 2002, February 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meeting notes Suzanne Sennett Feb 19, February 19, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - List of data needs and issues for class to address, February 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Letter Mary Dolan to Suzanne Sennett reserve fund, February 24, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fax Carol Smith NYS U Pre-K report, February 28, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fax Carol Smith NYS market rate report, February 28, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Class notes, March 3, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meeting notes Ariane Kissam and Sarah Crawford Mar 7, March 7, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Data matrix notes, March 11, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meeting notes methodologies and NYS data March 12, March 12, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Email Suzanne Sennett class update, March 14, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Proposal for geographic groupings, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Survey Questions outline and comments, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NACCRRA Report on NYS Child Care, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Methodologies for NACCRRAA NYS Child Care Report, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Child care subsidy co-pay calculations, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2002 NYS child care grants by county, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NYS child care provider wage estimates, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Source information on child care wages, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Summary of Child Care Economic Impact Studies (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Revised work plan proposal, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Survey calendar, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - VPK memo calendar, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Student assignments, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meeting notes data call, March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Class notes March 26, March 26, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Process meeting March 28, March 28, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Memo to class partners with data questions and attachments, March 28, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Memo to Technical Advisory Committee, March 28, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Class agenda week of March 31, March 31, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Class notes March 31 with attachments, March 31, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Class notes April 2 (Typed), April 2, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Class notes April 2 (Handwritten), April 2, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Email Economic Impact Study conference call, April 3, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Detailed workplan with April deadlines, April 3, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Class notes April 6, April 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Memo to class partners April 7, April 7, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Meeting notes partner meeting with attachments of work to date April 7, April 7, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Child Care as Economic Development Presentation to Child Care Bureau Research meeting, April 8, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Meeting notes partners April 11 with capacity matrix, April 11, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Email Suzanne Sennett updated CC R&R listings, April 11, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Class notes April 14, April 14, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - List of Upcoming due dates, April 14, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Email Ariane Kissam appointment times by group, April 15, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Memo to class partners with attachments April 22, April 22, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Executive Summary with comments, April 27, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Defining the Sector Report with comments, April 27, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Economic Development recommendations with comments, April 27, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Memo to class partners with attachments April 28, April 28, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Misc Notes, April 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Final NYS Report (brochure), June 26, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- New York State Child Care Resource and Referral Agency Survey Spring/Summer, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fax from Colleen Smith Market Rate Report, February 28, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - NYS R&R survey instrument, April 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Otsego County survey response, April 24, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Albany, Saratoga, Schenectady, Rensselaer survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Schoharie survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Putnam County survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Columbia-Greene survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chenago, Delaware,Otsego survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dutchess County survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Tompkins County survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Suffolk County survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Delaware County survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Orange county survey response, May 6, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chatauqua County survey response, May 9, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Suffolk County revised survey response, May 12, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Email Mildred Warner CCRR survey, May 19, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Steuben County survey response, May 19, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cayuga County survey response, May 27, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Seneca County survey response, May 27, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chenango County survey response, May 27, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Head Start NY data, June 11, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Memo from Amy Cooper with New York City survey response, June 12, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Email from Louise Stoney on survey data for 3 and 4 year olds, July 21, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Email from Louise Stoney on survey data from CDF, July 21, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Orleans County survey response, July 9, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Genesee County survey response, July 16, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fax from Celeste Frey Notes on child care regression model, August 7, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Meeting notes Zhilin Liu and initial model output, August 8, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Email to David Kay from Zhilin Liu requesting IMPLAN, August 11, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Email to David Kay IMPLAN Model meeting, August 13, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Meeting notes IMPLAN Model with handouts Aug 14, August 14, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - State ECE Workforce Estimates by Richard Brandon and Erin Maher, August 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Multiplier estimates, August 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Determinants of State Child Care Utilization Patterns for Estimating the Size of the Child Care Workforce at the State Level (Methodology), June 25, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Misc notes (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 50 State Model (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Memo variables for child care model with data sources/responsibility chart, August 28, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Model Building notes, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Powerpoint Presentation Differences in Economic Linkages of Child Care Sector, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Model Summary child care gross receipts, no total pop, no child care employment, no fed funds logged, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Model summary employment multiplier, no total pop, no gross receipts, no fed funds logged, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Regression output multipliers, only fed funds logged-no total pop or gross receipts, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Percentile Histogram Type 1 Employment Multiplier, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)